The whole world moves because of [music]
the currency exchange. Oh yeah, without
forks, the word would not work. Bullish.
>> Yes. Oh, this is crazy.
>> No, I didn't think I was going to get it
at first.
>> You'd be surprised how many people would
get that wrong.
>> Yeah, we about to change the profession.
>> I've had students taking [music] $1,000
to about $130,000 the first 3 weeks.
Then they'll blow that.
>> What's your advice if if I'm a student,
>> we weren't woke.
>> We just knew we had to go to school.
Man, I should have been doing this
instead of college.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to a very
interesting video. Today we're going to
be teaching the man, the myth, the
legend, Ashton Hall, how to trade today.
>> I'm ready.
>> And uh thank God I'm wearing a hoodie
cuz I'm feeling very small next to the
man right here cuz
>> you got the beard. You can't have
everything, brother. Come on now.
>> Well, today So, have you ever traded
before in your life?
>> Never.
>> Literally,
>> you have no experience. You never bought
crypto. You've never done anything.
>> I see people trading and I'm just like,
it's sign language. I see nothing.
>> Probably like Chinese, like different up
and down. I told my team I said if I'm
going to trade I'm going to do it with
Ali's G and we here.
>> Okay. All right. I appreciate that. I
appreciate you trusting in me. Right. So
today we're going to be teaching you how
to trade. I'm going to literally be
teaching you all the basics. What is
trading? How it works? How to execute a
trade. And uh at the end of it, you're
going to take three real trades. We're
going to go back testing and we're going
to put what I taught you to test.
>> If you catch one of the three trades
correct, you win because you're going to
be in the profitable. All this math will
make sense at the end. But if you get
all of them wrong, then you or I will
have to eat the world's hottest chip,
right? So the goal is to not eat this
chip. We got to stay away. We got to
stay safe.
>> So you got to pay attention to what I'm
going to be teaching you today. So with
that being said, are you ready?
>> 100%. Let's do it.
>> All right. Perfect. Okay. So when it
comes to the markets, there's multiple
different types of markets, right? So
you're going to have the forex market,
which is short for foreign exchange.
Don't mind my handwriting. So, Forex is
short for foreign exchange. Yeah. You
also have the stock market. You're also
going to have futures markets and then
you're also going to have crypto, right?
So, these are all very, very, very, very
different markets, right? At the end of
the day, they all represent price in the
form of a chart. You're going to see
lines that go up and down and all
they're doing is representing what is
happening on this specific markets in
the chart format. It's all the same
thing, right? Okay.
>> So, once you learn how to read this
chart format, you can pretty much trade
anything.
>> Yeah.
>> Because once you learn how to read the
charts, it's just being represented in
either foreign exchange, which is for
dollars.
>> So, for example, here you're going to
have, let's say, the euro versus the
USD.
>> Yeah. So the euro is going to be
fighting the USD. The USD is going to be
fighting the euro.
>> Okay?
>> So think about this as Mike Tyson
and then think of this as Holyfield,
right?
>> Okay.
>> Both of these guys are in a fight.
>> Yeah.
>> But think about this fight as it never
ends. It's literally a constant fight
that is going down 245. So foreign
exchange market is open 24 hours out of
the day for 5 days a week.
>> It's closed on the weekend, right? So
all this is the foreign exchange market.
>> So Holyfield and Mike Tyson are simply
fighting all the time. Sometimes Mike
Tyson gets a good uppercut. Sometimes
Holyfield gets a gut shot. Mike Tyson
might bite his ear. Something like that
might right? So, it's a fight that
happens constantly and you're basically
going to be betting Holyfield is going
to win
>> round number three
>> or Mike Tyson is going to win round
number five.
>> Yeah.
>> And there's never a winner. Like there's
the fight never ends. So, you're just
basically going to bet that they're
going to
>> one of the fighters is going to win for
the next two rounds, three rounds, four
rounds, so on.
>> Okay?
>> And that's going to reflect on the
market in terms of days. You think the
euro is going to beat the dollar for two
days, for one hour, for 15 minutes. You
can pretty much break it down as long as
you want.
>> Okay.
>> So, you think Mike Tyson is having
better stamina than Holyfield,
>> there's only two fields, Euro and then
USD.
>> Yeah. For the foreign exchange, this
example. Yeah. But it go there's endless
forex.
>> Yeah. For forex, you can have the GBP
USD, which is the pound versus the
dollar. Mhm.
>> You can have USD, JPY, which is the
dollar versus the Japanese yen.
>> Yeah.
>> It's endless amounts of different
markets, but the basis is the same.
>> So, when someone says they do forex,
they're trading.
>> They're trading. Yeah.
>> What do you do for a living? Forex. They
just trade.
>> Yeah. But at no point do you ever own
any one of these currency pairs
>> ever. All you're doing is just betting
that one of them is going to be stronger
than the other for a short period of
time
>> or a long period of time.
>> Okay.
>> That is forex trading.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Stock market is a little bit
different when it comes to the stock
market.
>> What's the best one?
>> Forex.
>> Yeah. I'll explain to you why. Right.
So,
>> because you can make the most.
>> You can make the most. It's open the
longest and you can have the lowest
entry barrier. So, you can start off
Forex with a 100 bucks
>> and you have leverage with a 1 to 500.
So, this is very important and I'm going
to explain why.
>> Yeah. So, with Forex, you can start off
with as little as a 100 bucks and you
have buying power of a 1 to500. So
meaning this $100 you have a multiplier
of 50 on it.
>> Okay?
>> So you this really is about $5,000 in
terms of buying power. So you can trade
as if it were to be much higher in your
account. Now obviously that you know
turns to more risk which this can get
lost a lot easier if for example if you
were to have a leverage of a 1 to 50.
>> Yeah.
>> But the opportunity to make more money
is a lot greater because you have more
leverage.
>> Yeah. When it comes to the stock market,
the minimum entry is going to be around
anywhere from $10,000
to $25,000.
And the leverage can be limited to a 1
to 25. So, you're really limited to a
very small amount of money of the money
you put in.
>> Yeah.
>> And you're going to require a lot more
money to get put in. And then the stock
market is five days a week from 9 to 5.
So your odds of trading, your hours of
trading are a lot less.
>> Yeah.
>> In the forex market 245 in the stock
market.
>> A lot of somebody hit the stock of the
uh forex
>> because some people like the idea of
trading the stock market because they
read a lot of fundamentals, right? So
the stock market is very influenced by
fundamentals,
>> right? Because the fundamentals are so
the stock market are companies. You're
buying into Apple, you're buying into
Tesla,
>> and it's more physical things in a way.
There's more reports that you can look
into.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's almost more of like a
longerterm play. You can trade it on on
the day trade as well, but people like
reading the fundamentals. When it comes
to the Forex market, it's a lot more
technical.
>> Yeah.
>> Because it's just currency markets,
right? So, you're just basing it off of
patterns in the markets. The same
patterns could happen in the stock
market, but it's much more influenced by
fundamentals, right? So this right here
is just a quick overview. When you have
futures, commodities, all this other
stuff, this is going to be stuff like
gold, you have silver, you have oil,
and you could also have NAS 100. So this
is basically you can also trade futures
in the forex market. Okay, same thing.
And in crypto obviously you have your
BTC, you have your ETH, Salana, and
never ending amounts of crypto.
>> Okay, if I were to rank these in order
for me, Forex would be number one,
crypto would be number two, futures
would be number three, and then the
stock market would be number four.
>> So you do more more of forex
>> foreign exchange market. Yeah.
>> And most people would agree with that.
>> I could argue that most people could
agree with that. Yeah. there's just
there's a lot more volatility, there's a
lot more options, there's a lot more
patterns as well.
>> And to me, there's a lot more
reliability simply because yeah, it's
just it just simply makes more sense and
from my humble experience. But lately,
I've been trading a little bit of of
futures and I don't really like trading
crypto. But
>> yeah, this is just want to give you like
an over idea of all the different type
of markets that there is. Now, we'll get
into a bit more of the technicals now.
>> Okay.
>> Do you have any questions on this so
far? Any concerns?
>> We're ready to hit big, man. M. So
basically, you're just betting on what's
going to be up.
>> It's pretty much just like sports
betting, right? But the game doesn't
end.
>> The game doesn't end. And there's real
patterns. Well, I mean, I guess you can
say there's also patterns with sports
betting in a way.
>> Like, let's say you see the team
>> line up momentum or some
>> Yeah. or like they do their lineup in a
specific way.
>> You see the market do a lineup in a
specific way. You can predict that
they're they're going to do a run or
they're going to do a pass
>> and you get paid off of them doing good
or bad or you lose money off of them
doing bad.
>> The sports team or the trading
>> trading.
>> Yeah, correct. Yeah. I mean, you're
basically betting.
>> So, where does the money come from? Like
if I'm betting that you're doing better
than someone else, who's paying?
>> Yeah. So, the money is coming from the
market. So, someone else is losing that
money indirectly.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. So, like someone else is getting
>> So, you're paying that they're doing
good. I'm paying that they're doing bad.
Correct. Yeah. There's always
>> if I if I win, your money goes to me. Te
kind of.
>> It's in it's in the air. Yes. But
technically, yes.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah. Like somebody there's always going
to be someone on the other side.
>> So it has nothing to do with the two
parties. The money is not coming from
them.
>> No.
>> The money is coming from the people who
are trading.
>> Correct.
>> So you're just trading against other
people who are trading.
>> Correct. Yeah. But that's crazy.
>> Okay. But this is something that I
wanted to add. The
>> How is that legal?
>> Yeah. Because
>> that's just like gambling, right?
>> No. No. So the forex market is a $6.7
trillion market. Not not billion.
Billion is down here.
>> 6.7 million.
>> Why? Who made this popular?
>> Because this is the currencies of the
world. Like this is the economy of of
the globe, you know, like you have the
euro, the pound, the dollar, the
Japanese yen, the Russian dollar, the
noggin, the Swiss Frank. Like
>> and people just became obsessed with
what's going to be up. you're you're
basically betting on the dollars of
these of these countries. So, this is
the biggest market because it's
literally the dollar of a country.
>> So, this is much bigger than just the
stock market because the stock market is
just the US.
>> This is just a billion dollar market.
>> This is a couple billion dollar market.
No, no comparison to a trillion dollar
market. So, there's a lot more
opportunity and volatility here.
>> This is the entire world. This is just
the US.
The US is very small compared to the
world's economy.
>> Do you think forex trading changes
anything to do with like how the world
operates?
>> This is how the world operates because
of the foreign exchange. If not, it
would never operate. Yeah. Like the
whole world moves because of the
currency exchange. Correct. Like money
being transferred from one country to
another. The stock market is just within
the US.
>> Right.
>> So you think the world needs forex?
>> Oh yeah. Without forex the world would
not work
>> really.
>> Yeah. You need to exchange currencies
all the time. When people travel, you go
to the airport, you know, you see the
the that currency exchange at those
spots.
>> Yeah. When you go there, you're
exchanging currencies all day.
>> That's what makes the world go around.
>> So, does this field make the most
millionaires?
>> I think so. Mine.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. 100%.
>> Wait, isn't there a fact? This should be
a fact.
>> Uh, I mean, we can search it out. Let me
see. Does the Forex market make the most
millionaires? Yes, the Forex market can
make you a millionaire. Many successful
traders have achieved sign significant
wealth through this expertise and
strategies in currency market. For
instance, Ray Valio is recognized as the
richest forex trader with a net worth of
$14 billion and George Soros with a net
worth of $8 billion.
>> These Yeah, these are the richest
traders in the world. You know, you know
what's funny? I knew they were the
richest traders in the world, but I
didn't know it was because of the Forex
market.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. I just found this out right now.
>> Damn.
>> Shout out to you.
>> Google. Shout out to Google. [laughter]
>> All right. So, when it comes to trading
any type of market, futures market,
stock market, crypto, or anything,
you're going to need three main things
to determine if entering the trade makes
sense.
>> Yeah.
>> Doesn't matter what you're trading,
doesn't matter if you're driving, if
you're sleeping, it doesn't matter. You
just need these three foundations to
take a trade.
>> Okay?
>> The simplest analogy that I can make
this to is if you're going to go surf,
right? When you go surf, you need three
things. You need an ocean. You need a
surfboard. And then most importantly,
you need the right wave to go surf.
>> Yeah,
>> those are the three things that you need
to surf.
>> Okay,
>> when you go enter a trade, you need
three things. You need the trend,
>> you need an area of interest, and you're
going to need your entry signal.
>> So, trading is very similar to surfing,
>> if not exactly the same.
>> But you're not getting risk of getting
eaten by a shark, right? So
>> trading
is like surfing.
One is going to be trend
which is going to be the ocean
current.
Two is going to be area of interest
which is going to be the beach.
And then three is going to be entry
signal
which is going to be the actual wave
to enter or to surf. Right.
>> Yeah. This first one is the trend which
is how is the market moving?
>> Yeah.
>> Is the market moving up or is the market
moving down? Based off of the trend
you're able to understand if you want to
buy or sell.
>> Okay. A lot of people when they just
look at the market, they just say it's
going to go up or it's going to go down,
but they can't really tell you why.
>> So, there's a way of identifying the
trend, and that's going to be based off
of market
structure.
The market structure is literally the
heart of the market. Without the market
structure, the mark the trend currency
like it doesn't nothing exists.
>> Yeah. So this right here, what you're
seeing these triangles up or down, these
arrows up or down, that is market
structure.
>> Picture that as if it were to be the
trail of when somebody is walking in the
snow. You know, when somebody walks in
the snow, they leave these little
footsteps.
>> Yeah.
>> This is the footsteps of the market when
it's going up or when it's going down.
>> But instead of it being called
footsteps, it's called market structure.
>> Okay? So picture the trend the market
structure as the waves
currents either going east or going west
for example right so there's a terrible
forms of waves so you have a visual when
you're going to go surf you're either
surfing to this side of the coast or
you're surfing to this side but you have
to follow wherever the ocean's going or
the current's going right
>> area of interest is going to be
literally what it's called area of
interest which is a zone where it's
going to make the most sense to enter
the trade because just because you see a
market going up or a market going down
doesn't mean you just jump into the
market.
>> You need to wait for it to get to a
specific zone. Yeah.
>> Right. So that specific zone is where
you're going to enter the trade. So
let's say the market is trending upwards
and yes the even though the market might
be at a high point you need to wait for
it to come back to this area of interest
for then here to you take the trade. So
this area of interest is the most common
mistake traders make when it comes to
patience. They don't wait for the market
to get back to this area.
>> When it comes to the ocean, it's the
beach. Because a lot of traders, uh, a
lot of surfers when they go to the
beach, they think that just where you
park your car is where you can surf the
wave.
>> No, you have to walk down a beach a
little bit, maybe walk a little bit more
west, a little bit more east, or even
surf a little bit out so you catch the
right area where the waves are being
formed.
>> Okay? You can't just surf off of the
beach. You can't just surf wherever you
want. It's wherever the waves are being
formed. So, you you need to make sure
that you're at the right spot.
>> Correct. At the at the right area on the
beach.
>> So, this is probably the sand where this
is my version of a palm tree. So, if
these are the waves, you need to make
sure if you're right here, you need to
make sure that you go to where the waves
are. Yeah. Can't just surf from wherever
you want. And then lastly, most
importantly, is the entry signal. It's
the reason why you enter. Entry signals
can consist of many different types of
things. They can consist of
>> dogey rejections and engulfing
rejection. So, this is a candle going up
or down. This will make sense once I
actually show you the technicals of it.
>> But this is the reason why you enter the
trade. Same exact thing when it comes to
the surfing. You know, you can be on the
surfboard, but you need to make sure
that you actually see the wave incoming
from far and that it makes sense for you
to paddle to this wave and kick yourself
onto the wave.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that wave being formed or a crevice
being formed from far is what's going to
tell you to get onto that wave or that
it's ready to go. The market gives you a
crevice from far, letting you know that
it's ready to enter the trade as well.
>> Okay.
>> All right. So, do you understand all
this so far?
>> Yeah, for the most part.
>> Okay. Any questions on this right now?
>> Not right now.
>> Not right now. Okay, perfect. So, keep
in mind trend, area of interest, and
entry signal. Now, we're going to
dissect every single one of these
details where it's going to be easier
than ever. Just kind of went over the
top right now to give you a visual, but
this is everything you need to learn to
be able to properly enter a trade and
understand if it makes sense to take the
trade or not. So, back to the trading,
right? So, we got here trading. So, the
first thing is going to be the trend,
right?
>> Yeah. So we under trend we understand
that the trend is also equal to market
structure
which is also equal to the heart.
>> This is the pulse of the market.
>> Yeah.
>> The market will create a pulse to the
upside. The market will create a pulse
to the downside.
>> Yeah.
>> Now in an actual heartbeat it's called a
pulse. Right? Yeah. If you look at a
spell pulse wrong,
pulse. If you look at a pulse of a
heart, you know, you see like
that's the pulse of your heart, right?
It'll be something like this. It'll be
like this. It have a spike. That's the
pulse of the heart.
>> Yeah.
>> The market structure reflects a pulse in
the same way, but it's not called a
pulse.
>> It's called
HH HL
L.
probably wondering what the hell is
that?
>> Yeah,
>> very easy, right? This is not
complicated. It's very simple. HH is
equal to higher high.
HL
is equal to a higher low.
LH is equal to a lower
high.
And then LL is equal to a lower
low, right? Yeah. Higher high, higher
low, lower low, and lower high. Now,
these at no point do they ever go
together. Yeah. Not all of them. These
are This is the brother. This is the
sister. These always go together. These
always go together.
>> These go together when the market is
bullish.
Bullish equals
buys. Yeah, this is when the market is
bearish. When the market is bearish, it
equals sells.
You can only have So, these actually get
split right down the middle.
>> Yeah.
>> So, a bullish market consists of higher
highs and higher lows. A bearish market
consists of lower highs and lower lows.
>> Okay?
>> You can never have these combined,
right? It's just this is this. A boy is
a boy, a girl is a girl.
>> Simple. So a bullish market which would
be this right here when the market is
going up is consisted of what is this
>> higher
>> higher high
>> and higher low
>> higher low.
>> So when something is a higher high is
that it's the highest high. So this
right here would be a higher high.
>> Yeah
>> because that's the highest point.
>> So what is a higher low? Well it's the
last highest low. Now, if I were just to
follow back on this market right here,
>> higher high is what you get paid off of.
>> Higher high is just where
>> if you're betting that they're going up,
>> correct? Yes. But like right now, what
we want to do is just understand what's
the pulse of the market. What's the
market structure? Is the market up or is
the market down?
>> And you cannot identify, right? I'm
going to write this here.
>> You cannot
identify
if the market
is up or down
without market structure.
>> That's market structure.
>> Correct. So basically higher high is
just showing that it's already high but
it would even it went even higher than
its high high.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> And it tells you where it is. It tells
you it's at the highest point. It's at
the lowest point. It's in the middle.
This tells you where the market is,
right?
>> That's the graph that you see.
>> Correct.
>> So if I see the graph like that and then
it goes up, this is a higher low. That
would be a higher That would be a higher
high because so if it's like this and
then it goes down but it's like that but
it was up here
>> then it's a higher low.
>> It depends on how it breaks it and it's
all going to make sense right now. Okay.
>> Right. Okay. That's a great question by
the way. It's good that you're asking
that right now. Right. So the highest
the higher high it's obviously the
highest point.
>> Now the higher low is the next spot
which would be this point right here.
That right there would be a higher low.
All you have to do is follow backwards
the last from the higher high. You
simply follow it back and it's going to
tell you where the higher low is.
>> Okay.
>> So, for right now, we're going to make
this the higher low. So, we're going to
do it right here, right? In a much
bigger scale just so it's much cleaner.
So, this right here is the higher high.
This right here is the higher low.
>> Okay. So, the higher high is just the
highest point
>> as of right now. Yes. So, this market is
bullish because of this higher high and
higher low. The moment we break below
this higher low, this market is no
longer bullish. So that was your
question on the bearish example and
it'll make sense right now, right? So if
this market for whatever reason does
something like this, it's no longer
bullish because it has broken below the
higher low.
>> Bullish is making making it that it's
up.
>> Correct.
>> Bullish means it's up.
>> Bullish means it's up. So, as long as we
are in between this higher low and this
higher high, we're bullish. So, this
market can have a retracement to here.
>> Oh, okay. We're still up.
>> Yeah. Right now, we're still bullish
because we're still in between the
higher high and the higher low.
>> We still win it.
>> Yeah. If this market does this, cool. We
just broke the last
>> higher high.
>> We have a new higher high. Correct. So,
this is the new higher high. And then
the new higher low gets moved to the
next higher low.
>> Alex, I'm ready.
>> No, hold on. Hold on.
All right, hold on. [laughter] Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Right. So,
this right now would turn into the new
higher low, right?
>> Mhm.
>> So, that's the new higher low. This
point right here. Once again, this
market does something like this. It
breaks above this point right here. This
is the higher high. This is the higher
low. And as long as we remain inside of
this move right here, we will be
bullish. Right?
>> So, as long as we are inside of this
higher high and higher low, we are
bullish. So if this market does
something like this, you can Yeah, that
is bullish. Correct. But you cannot
count. So right now, let's say we open
up price and we see this, right? So
let's say we see a naked a naked price
on the market right now, right? We open
up trading view, which is where we
analyze the charts.
>> Man, I should have been doing this
instead of college. No, [laughter]
>> wait. I was in college 6 years ago. Hey,
you teach me none of this.
>> Wait, what did you study in college?
>> I studied everything. I switched my
major every every semester.
>> Oh, nice. You dropping classes left and
right. [laughter] I should have been in
school, Alex. Come on, bro. I should
have been right here instead of them six
years at UCF and Alorn State. Come on,
man.
>> Do you even use anything that you
learned?
>> Nothing, bro. I learned nothing. I was
just there just trying to make it to
class on time.
>> Yeah,
>> it was none of this.
>> No. No, bro. I didn't learn this in
college either.
>> I dropped out and after like 3 months, I
didn't really make it at all.
>> I think now people know like cuz when
back in my day, I'm 30. back then if you
didn't go to college. Oh, Jared didn't
go to college, bro. He's tripping like
he's a failure.
>> Now it's like if you're in college at
this age, 18, 19, it's like, oh, you're
getting scammed.
>> Yeah.
>> People know they're catching on.
>> Yeah. Like it's more
>> even like the the multi
multi-millionaire Alexi, they're saying
school college is scam.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. Cuz like back then when you were
in college, there wasn't no social
media. People weren't posting.
>> There was no social media, so we weren't
woke.
>> We just knew we had to go to school if
we didn't go to school. Even if we
didn't know what we were doing, we
needed to be in school. Mhm.
>> It's crazy.
>> Well, yeah. This is going to save some
people a lot of money.
>> Should have been here, bro. All right,
let's get it.
>> All right. So, when you come to identify
this market to understand if this is
bullish or bearish,
>> you can't look at this point right here,
right? Cuz that right there, you can't
mark this off as the higher low.
>> It's not a higher low because a higher
low mandatory needs a higher high.
Mandatory,
>> right? Mandatory. The higher low needs
the higher high. Mhm.
>> So if you mark this as the higher low,
you can't mark the higher high behind
the higher low.
>> That makes no sense.
>> This is not a higher low cuz it's still
bullish.
>> Correct. Yeah. This right here
>> until it goes down there.
>> Yeah. Correct. This right here would be
the higher low.
>> This right here would be
>> higher high.
>> Higher high. Correct. Now if we delete
all this right here and let's say this
market once again, let's say it does
this. This market is still bullish
because we are inside of the higher low
and we're inside of the higher high.
Right? The moment this market breaks
below the higher low, we are no longer
bullish.
>> Yeah. This market has what's called
shift of structure. SOS.
So it's SOS one because it's called
shift of structure. But this is really
really like this is literally a red
flag, right? because you need to
understand that this is now changing
which is very important cuz it can turn
something from buying to selling within
a second.
>> So SOS is a very big deal because you
know red flag sirens going everywhere.
You no longer are looking for buys. Now
you're looking for
>> wait that back. SOS is what now?
>> SOS is shift of structure. So shift
>> that's when it goes down is under
bullish
>> of structure. Yes. That's when the
structure changes. So this is this right
here is the structure.
>> Yeah. This right here is the pulse.
>> This is SOS.
>> Yeah. SOS because it's a shift of
structure. The market just changed from
bullish to bearish.
>> Okay. Even if it's down and goes up,
it's still SOS.
>> Correct. And I'm I'm going to explain
that now. Right. Right. Now why? Right.
So shift structure is very important
because the mark it's literally giving
you the SOS that this market is no
longer doing what it was supposed to. So
right now we know that's bullish.
>> This is the higher low which is very
important. Once this market breaks that
higher low, we're now bearish because
this market has now just created
a lower low, which is over here. When
the market is bearish, it creates a
lower low and a lower.
>> Bullish is still
>> No, bullish would be
>> it's still it's it's not breaking. It's
still up.
>> Yeah, bullish would be if it breaks back
above this right here. And I'll explain
it right now. Right. So this is where
things get a little tricky but as soon
as you understand this literally you
understand everything if you get this
because this is the pulse of the market.
I would put I'd say 80% focus of
learning how to trade on this. You could
get everything else
>> on the trend.
>> On the trend. Right. So right now
>> the trend is pretty much what everybody
sees those.
>> Correct. Correct.
>> If you know what that means, then you
good to trade.
>> You got everything. Yeah. So that's the
higher low. That's the higher high. We
got that.
>> Yeah.
>> Whenever we break below the higher low,
>> bearish.
>> We're bearish.
>> And now when this market goes bearish,
>> right? Okay. So, we just mark it off
like this. This now becomes the lower
low and this now becomes the lower high.
>> Okay.
>> So, lower high.
>> But if we break below the the the higher
low,
>> the lower high. Yeah. If we break above
the lower high, we're back to bullish.
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> Correct. Right. So, let's run this back
right here. Right. So, this market
is now bearish.
>> This is that higher high, though.
>> Was the higher high when the market
shifted this structure point right here.
Now it's the lower high.
>> Yeah. Now the market's bearish. And when
the market is bearish, it mandator
>> turns into the lower high. Correct.
>> Okay.
>> So as long as we are in between.
>> So when if it was bullish, if it would
have stopped right here, this still
would have been a higher high.
>> Correct.
>> Okay.
>> Yes. So yes, correct. If if the Yes, you
got it. You're actually getting it
pretty easy. I did not expect that. I'm
not going to lie. I'm not going to lie.
Right. So this market right here is now
bearish. This is the lower low. This is
the lower high. We could do in here all
this fidazzle, whatever you want. We're
still bearish because we have a lower
low, lower high.
>> Let's say the market right here breaks
below. We are continuation are bearish.
>> So this now becomes right. I'm going to
do this like this. This market does this
like this.
>> Market messed up bad.
>> Yeah. But you can make money off the
sales too. Yeah. So right now
>> you just got to guess, right?
>> You make a very highly educated guess.
>> Yes. Yeah. So this right here would
become our lower low and then our lower
high would just follow price back.
Whenever we see that pulse that market
structure that now becomes our lower
high. So this market is bearish as long
as we remain inside of here.
>> Mhm.
>> Same exact thing. We break below again
>> new lower low and then new lower high.
So this goes to both of these right
here. Whenever you break as a new lower
low, you always need a new lower high.
>> Okay?
>> Whenever you break for a new higher
high, you always need a new higher low.
>> Okay?
>> Right? So, for example, let's say over
here, got a lot of lines going on,
right? Let's delete all these nonsense
ones. So, it's like very clean when it
comes to the mark. Like the less
information, like the less stuff you
have in your charts, the better. So,
right now, this is the lower low. This
is the lower high. If this market does
this, what happens?
>> We're SOS.
>> Yes. Yo, I didn't I did not think you
were going to say it. I'm not even
kidding,
>> bro. Yes, we are. Yo, for real. I did
not expect that. I'm I'm not even
capping right now. Yes, we are SOS.
>> Big problem. We have a shift of
structure. What happens when you have a
shift of structure?
>> Cuz we were bearish. So, when a shift of
structure, what happens?
>> Oh, we're uh bullish.
>> Yes. so much.
>> Yo, this is crazy. Yo, I'm not I'm not
even like capping.
>> We're locked in,
>> brother. I am I'm not even kidding,
dude. You'd be surprised how many people
would get that wrong,
>> guys. We about to change the profession.
>> Yo, damn, bro. I'm not even like hyping
you up right now.
>> No, I didn't think I was going to get it
at first. I'm like, damn. I don't know
all these charts and stuff like that.
>> I'm sure there's a lot more stuff I need
to learn to be able to trade, though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, but dude, you get
>> But I'm just getting the concept,
>> brother. You you're you're getting it
faster than I got it, bro. Like, it took
for me to understand what you're
understanding right now. didn't have you
as a coach.
>> No, I I just had Bro, bunch of random
YouTube videos, bro.
>> Sometimes it's better to learn the hard
way.
>> Correct. Yeah,
>> cuz you feel the pain and now you can
like feel how good it is to be up.
>> Mhm. Mhm. No, I I agree. Now that we
have this SOS, we're back to bullish.
So, this is now the higher high. This is
now the higher low, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Easy higher low. Easy higher high. Once
again, this market can simply just have
this retracement here. We're still
bullish.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. We can do something like this.
We're still bullish. We can do something
like this. We're still bullish because
we are yet to break above or below the
higher low and the higher high.
>> Okay. So, if we go down, we're bearish.
But if we go up, we're still bullish.
But it's SOS.
>> No, it's No, SOS is when it goes from a
boy to a girl or a girl to a boy.
>> Okay. Okay. So, we're still just
bullish.
>> It's just a higher high.
>> Correct.
>> Okay,
>> bro. Bro,
you teaching me good, bro.
>> Bro, hold on. All right. So, yes. So if
this decides to do this, it's not a
shift to structure. Just it's a
continuation of this. Yeah.
>> So this turns into the new higher high.
>> This right here turns into the new
higher low.
>> Okay.
>> Easy.
>> 100%.
>> That right there is trend. That is how
you identify if something's bullish or
bearish.
>> All right. So we're going to put it to
the test real quick. Right. Pop up a
clean chart and I want you to identify
for me if this market is bullish or if
this market is bearish. Right. Yeah, I
can get some horizontal, too. Do both.
>> All right.
>> All right. Is this market bullish or is
this market bearish?
>> Oh, this where it gets real. All right.
Is it bullish or bearish?
[laughter]
Remember what we spoke about. I remember
I should have I should have I should
have explained something before, but
it's okay. I I'll wait. You It's good if
you make a mistake.
>> I'll say bullets. I mean, not bearish.
>> Okay. Why? Where's the lower high?
Where's the low?
>> This is the high and it broke down.
>> Okay. Show me. Go ahead. Mark it off.
>> So, it's the higher high right here.
>> Remember, uh, bearish or bullish?
>> Uh, you said bearish.
>> Bearish.
>> Okay. Okay. Remember, bearish, lower
high, lower low. So, it can be a higher
high. If it's bearish, it's a lower
high.
>> Oh, higher high.
>> So, will you say it's bullish or if it's
bearish?
>> Bullish.
>> Okay. Go ahead.
Draw the horizontal lines. It's the most
important thing.
>> Remember, look, this is a perfect
bullish example. Draw the higher high
with a line across.
Are you rethinking?
>> So, more so right here.
>> Yes.
>> Right.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Okay. So, it's not bearish.
>> Yeah.
>> So, bullish.
>> This market would be bullish.
>> Okay.
>> Correct.
>> Only thing that was throwing me was cuz
it went it broke this line right here.
right there. So I was thinking it was
bearish.
>> It was bearish but because
>> but then it came back up and it
>> went back over.
>> Yeah. So like it it would have a line
like this. Sure. So that that would be
the lower high. It broke above. So yes,
it
>> So this was the higher high at one
point. Then when it broke up under this,
it became bearish, right?
>> Yes. And then that became the lower
high.
>> That became the lower high. Oh, and then
it broke against the lower high. So now
it's bullish again.
>> Now it's bullish again. Yes. sense.
>> So, this market was bullish for this
move right here. It was bearish for this
move right here and then it went back to
bullish because of that move right
there.
>> Yes.
>> Now, let's say it stopped right here.
It's still not bullish.
>> No, that's that's not higher than that,
right?
>> It is. It is higher. Oh, no. If it stops
still bearish.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Or there.
>> Yo, I don't think you understand, bro.
>> There [laughter] are there.
>> Yo, I don't think you understand, dude.
I I'm I'm genuinely
>> I thought I was lost and I was like,
"Okay, now I I got this." So, we got to
do that one more time.
>> I mean, brother, you literally asked all
the right qu you said everything
correct. So, yes, if this is bullish
right there, it shifts to bearish.
>> So, this could do this as long as it
doesn't break above that.
>> Still bearish.
>> Still bearish. And for the example, I
said it did break it.
>> Now, we're bullish.
>> So, now it's back to bullish.
>> Yeah,
>> brother. Oh, we're locked in.
>> No, no, no, no. You you you [__] it
up. Like, I'm not even kidding.
[laughter]
>> All right. So to your first original
question and like I I really want to
double down on trend because again
everything that we do from this point
forward
>> is being dictated because of the trend.
So for example like bro this puts it in
perspective though cuz it's like
>> I've never traded ever.
>> So if this is my first time watching
this video just because oh I want to
watch a hall whatever. If he can learn
it why the freak not me.
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> Correct.
>> Yeah. That's crazy. I like this. I like
this model. That is cool
>> because like is I I need you to
understand the power of like this right
here. The trend like this is what 99% of
surfers when they go to the beach to go
surf, they need to determine where are
the waves going. Are the waves going
this way or are the waves going this
way?
>> If you know
>> to catch the wave the right way, you
need to know the the motion.
>> Yeah. If you know the waves are going
that way, brother, you just go that way.
You find the perfect wig to get and
that's it. You know, that is where the
main focus should be on. The main focus
should be to understand where the trend
is going. So how do you guess the
market?
>> Well, this is the first thing is
understanding where the movement is
going and then you just have to find
that sweet spot to enter which is going
to be the next spot which is the area of
interest.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. So I just want to quiz you one
more on the first example that you
originally set which was if the market
is going down and it does this
is this market bullish or is it bearish?
>> Bearish.
>> Wrong.
>> Really
>> wrong. I'm glad you're wrong.
>> But it didn't go over this though.
>> No, but remember
>> if it's going down
>> Yeah. Okay. But this was the lower high.
This was the lower low.
>> Yeah.
>> It broke below that one. This becomes
the new lower low. The new lower high.
Price broke below this one.
>> The new lower low. New lower high.
>> Is that because it's consistently going
down at the same rate?
>> Yeah. So, new lower highs and lower lows
are being made.
>> So, this is a new lower high.
>> Correct.
>> And it broke that. So, that's why it's
bullish.
>> Correct.
>> That makes sense.
>> You bro, you see? Wow. That was like
literally what I just did right there.
This example right here of this doing
this
is no different of this example of me
doing this that you claimed it to be
bearish
>> cuz that was the higher low. That was
the higher high. It broke below.
>> Mhm.
>> This is the same thing. This was the
lower high. This is the lower low.
>> And it finally cracked that.
>> It literally if we just flipped this
whiteboard around, it would show the
same thing.
>> That makes sense, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Perfect.
That was I honestly I am more excited
about this than I I don't even
>> I'm I haven't seen any other like videos
or I haven't even looked into trading
ever. I always said I'm not going to
like dabble into that
>> always. So I don't know how good I'm
doing but
>> you're doing so does this make you feel
better just to understand the direction
of the market
>> 100%.
>> Okay, perfect. So when it comes to the
trend you're going to see and this is
just like to wrap up the trend part.
You're gonna see, you're not gonna see
price clean like this.
>> You're gonna see a lot of price. You're
gonna see this.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You're gonna see so much price action
that you're going to get confused.
>> Makes it harder to read.
>> Correct. Like even myself, I would see
this and I'
>> Well, I used to I would be overwhelmed,
right? Because there's just so much
going on. And this is where traders get
confused. They're like, "Okay, yeah,
over here it was here and then here it
was here and here was here." And yes,
all those points are relevant. They're
obviously valid, but price right now is
over here.
>> Over here.
>> So, none of that really matters
>> to a certain
>> I mean to read it.
>> Yes.
>> To see where the next move is, that
matters, but to see where the bearish or
bullish is over here.
>> Yes. Correct. So, whenever you want to
analyze the market, you want to focus
more or less on this area over here,
right? You don't you don't need to look
super far back when it comes to this,
right?
>> So,
>> beautiful. I mean that right there is
the trend. So this is going to be the
first thing. So the key takeaways from
trend are going to be it is the market
structure of the market. It's the pulse.
The pulse is reflected by higher highs
and higher lows.
>> Lower highs and lower lows. Whenever the
market goes from bullish
>> to then bearish that is called a shift
of structure.
>> Yeah.
>> Big red flag. the market is, you know,
screaming, letting you know we are no
longer looking to buy. So now you should
go look for sells because we've had a
ship to structure and you cannot
identify if the market is up or down
without market structure.
>> Wow.
>> You need to identify the higher high and
higher low. Lower higher lower low to
properly identify if the market is
bullish or bearish.
>> Oh no.
>> Perfect. Any questions? Any concerns?
>> Perfect. So second thing is going to be
a OI.
Area of interest is
also known
as support and resistance.
Support and resistance,
supply and demand zone
and order blocks.
This is all the same thing.
>> Mhm.
>> A supply and demand zone is an area
where you're looking for supply and an
area of demand zone is where you're
looking for the demand. Support and
resistance, supply and demand. Order
blocks, it's all the same thing. This an
order block is a block which is an area
of interest. Supply and demand is an
area where there's supply and demand. A
support and resistance is an area where
support and resistance. An area of
interest is an area of interest. It's
all the same thing. And I want to
explain this to you because the trading
industry lately has had an abundance of
people getting creative with different
ways on how to educate this
>> and they just over complicated it
because at the end of the day they all
have the same function. An area of
interest is an area of supports or an
area of resistance.
>> It's where the market if it's below it's
going to reject and whenever the market
is above it's simply going to reject.
Mhm.
>> So, whenever the market approaches an
area and it goes the opposite way,
there's clearly something there that's
pushing it down.
>> So, like let's say right now we had a
ceiling over our head and we're trying
to stand up. We can't cuz there's a
ceiling over our head.
>> That's a resistance.
>> And let's say we want to stand up. We're
going to push off of this table. This is
our support. We're going to push
ourselves up.
>> So, the support is what pushes price up.
The resistance is what pushes price
down. Mhm.
>> That's support and resistance, right?
So, resistance holds price down. Support
holds price up. Now, you can also have
resistance be used as support and then
push price up. So, for example, let's
say we were to be below this table right
now. If we'd want to get up, we would
hit our head. We can't get up. But if we
were to get the table
>> below us, we then would use ourselves to
get up. So, you can use this resistance
as support to push ourselves up. Okay.
>> So, resistance could be turned into
support
>> and then if something is a support, it
could then be used as resistance to go
to the downside.
>> Mhm.
>> That an area that is used as resistance
and support is what's called an AOI,
an area of interest. Mhm.
>> It's an area where you are interested to
either sell
>> if you're below or buy if you're above.
>> Sell if you're below.
Buy
if you're above.
This is very simple
>> and finding it. Well, any questions with
this so far?
>> No.
>> Very simple, right? Roof, floor. That's
how you think about it.
If you are below that is going to be the
roof which is equal to resistance.
And then if you're going to buy this is
going to be the floor. It's going to be
support. So it's going to be holding you
up. Right. And then both of these work
together which is what makes up an area
of interest. Both of these combined are
an area of interest.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. So the problem with 99% of
traders is that they don't know how to
identify properly an area of interest
and they identify an area of interest
very incorrectly and I'm going to
simplify for people in 5 seconds right
so the first things first you understand
that the market is
uh bullish correct so this is the higher
high this is the higher low right what
if I told you if the market is bullish
You should only be looking for buys
obviously, right? Yeah.
>> You can't be looking for sells if the
market's bullish.
>> You need to place the area of interest
within this higher high and within this
higher low.
>> What happens with 99% of traders is
they'll see this market that is going to
the upside
and then what they'll say is
>> they'll put it to the top.
>> Yeah. For example, Yeah. They'll put an
area of interest up here or they'll put
an area of interest over here for
example
>> like you know what I want to buy when
price gets here. So what they say is all
right I want to wait for price to come
back into this area. Once it comes back
into this area I'm going to buy.
>> But what's the problem with that? That
that is the higher low and guess what
happens when the market gets there?
>> There's a shift of structure.
>> It's bearish.
>> So you can't be buying in a market
that's bearish. Mhm.
>> So that's the problem with 99% of
traders that they simply place the areas
of interest incorrectly. You need to
place the areas of interest inside of
the higher high and inside of the higher
low. So an area of interest is where the
market has had three or more touches. So
area of interest equals three or more
touches. What is a touch?
For example,
this right here is a touch. You have one
touch right here. The market rejected it
once.
>> Marketer rejected it two times,
>> three times.
>> Mhm.
>> That is a valid area of interest.
>> That means area of interest that's
that's where it kind of stuck.
>> Correct. So obviously price right now is
not at that area of interest,
>> but that's where they've been majority
of the time.
>> Correct. Now that's where you have to
wait for the market to get there for you
to take your trade. Mhm.
>> But for example here, if this market,
right, we know that that's the higher
high, that's the higher low. If the
market makes it to that area of
interest, we're now bearish. So we can't
sell at a support, right? So like it's
like you jumping into a two-ft pool.
>> You're you're going to break your nose,
right?
>> Yeah.
>> You need to be able to have more depth
to it.
>> So an area of interest is what just has
more than three touches. So if I look
over here, I can just place, you know,
for examples purposes, we'll just bring
this one a little bit more up
like this. You can see that this right
here is an area
>> of interest.
>> Of interest, correct? It has been used
as resistance once, twice, and three
times.
>> So it makes the most amount of sense to
wait for price to come back into this
area,
>> right?
>> And that's where you would buy. That's
your area of interest. So perfect
analogy is you have
>> when you buy you're buying that what
what are you buying?
>> What do you mean?
>> You said you buy right here when it gets
back into the area of interest. But like
>> what
you're you're So at no point do you
actually buy a currency per you're just
betting that it's going to go up.
>> Oh you're okay. So you when you buy
you're betting it's going to go up.
Sometimes you can bet that it's going
down.
>> Yeah. You that that's where you would
sell. Correct.
>> Oh when you sell.
>> It's the same thing like Well, when you
sell
>> Okay. You sell when it's going down.
When you think it's going to go down you
sell. buy when you think it's going to
go up.
>> Correct. Correct. Yes. Yes.
>> You make more money selling or buying.
>> Same thing. Same thing. Yeah. I I
personally make more money when I'm
selling. I'm just a better seller. I
don't know why.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. That just
>> I know when it's about to go down,
though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I can spot easier when
it's going to go down. Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> So,
>> but not everybody is a better seller.
Some people are better buyers.
>> Some people are better buyers. Yeah.
>> Everybody's different when it comes to
that. Damn. It's the weirdest [__] ever.
Honestly, it's like if you're going to
go uh surf, some people Have you ever
snowboarded?
>> No. Mhm.
>> You ever skateboarded?
>> Yeah, a little bit.
>> Okay. You know when you go skateboard,
you either goofy or the other one,
whatever. It's the same thing. Some
people are better with their right foot
forward or the left foot forward.
>> Ali or something like that. Yeah.
>> No, Ali is when you jump.
>> Ali or Nali.
>> Oh, Ali or Nali. Yeah. Correct. Correct.
Correct. Yeah. It's the same thing.
>> So, this is an area of interest which is
the resistance of price. Right. So, this
right now, if you're below it, you're
going to go down. But if price is above
it, you're going to have a push up.
>> Okay.
>> That is literally how you find an area
of interest. It's within the higher high
>> and higher low now.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. That's it. It's very easy to find
it.
>> For example,
>> it has to be within the higher higher
higher low.
>> Yeah. For example, let's [cough] say
like this is one because it's right
there to even
>> Yeah. But that one would be bearish. So,
you would have to wait for price
>> to get below that area to sell,
>> come back, retest it, and then sell.
Correct.
>> For example, right here, bullish or
bearish?
>> Uh, bearish.
>> Amazing. Right. So, you know, that's the
lower high, that's the lower low. So, if
this market is bearish,
>> you need to look for sells.
>> Now, you would work inside of this right
here. You would work inside of this
lower high and inside of this lower high
and this lower low to look for that area
of interest.
>> There's not one though. So here, for
example, if we were to just start like
hovering price right here, that's not
one because it only has one touch.
>> If we go to this one right here,
>> that's two.
>> This one would have three.
>> You have one.
>> Oh, so that's the area of interest.
Okay. Cuz you can count if it's going
down, too.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You can you can count
touches above or touches below or above.
Correct.
>> Does it have to be exactly even or not?
Really?
>> No. So close.
>> Yeah. That that that's why like you
never do like an exact line. You do you
do like a little zone, a box,
>> kind of box it off, right?
>> Cuz it'll never be perfect.
>> It'll never be perfect. Correct. And
then here, you would wait for price to
have a retracement into here and then
that's where you would then be looking
to sell.
>> Okay.
>> That's it.
>> So, you're waiting for it to go up and
you're guessing. You're pretty much
going to guess its peak.
>> Yeah.
>> Before it drops.
>> You guess its peak. Yes. That's great.
You guess its peak and then at here is
basically where you wait for then the
next step which is the entry signal.
that then from that is the area that
it's going to go down one because so if
I if I bet right here that it's going to
drop
>> right here but it continues to go up I
lost. I thought if I thought it was
going to do that and I tried to sell
right here I'm done.
>> You Yes.
>> I would lose money.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. But if I bet right here that it
was going to drop and actually drop
>> Mhm.
>> I sold then I would make money.
>> Yes.
>> But if it went out then I would lose.
>> You would lose. Yes. It just simply
makes more sense to take the cell here
than here or here because there is a
historic pattern that whenever we're
below this area we go down.
>> Mhm.
>> There is not as much
>> background from here that it goes down
from there.
>> So you wait for it right when it hits
that same little peak.
>> Yes.
>> And say, "Oh, that's a ceiling." They
call it
>> a resistance.
>> The resistance. They're not They're not
breaking the resistance.
>> Correct. Correct.
>> Cuz why would they?
>> Why? Yeah. if historically whenever we
approach it.
>> But obviously they're bound to break it
at some point. So you're not you're
betting that they're not doing it yet.
>> Correct. Correct. And well the first
thing is you have the trend in your
favor. So that that is already giving
you more odds that this is going to
start going down. Right. This is just
having that retracement and then two you
have the area of interest that
>> trading is all about selling and buying
just period. Yeah.
>> I can trade it right now.
>> Yeah. You can trade whenever. Yeah.
You're just betting that it's going to
go up or down. I mean, bro, it's already
a 50/50. It's head or tails. Like, it's
really like
>> Well, I just put down like 10,000 or so.
>> Yeah, you can put 10,000. Yeah.
>> Every trade.
>> We're just betting 10,000.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I risk like 150 per trade.
>> We're going to start with 10,000.
[laughter]
>> No, but what I'm saying is start with
10,000. I'm not you.
>> No, no, I know. I know. But, but I'm
saying you could, but don't get too
hyped yet. I know. It's just I know. No,
no, just [laughter]
>> that's very No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's so much more that goes into it.
>> Stay home. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. But what
matters when it comes to the area of
interest for all you got to do is sell
if you're below,
>> buy if you're above.
>> Yeah.
>> So, right here, we're bearish and we're
going to be below it. It just makes more
sense to sell.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. All right. So, let's say this
market
>> you've seen somebody inexperience just
hit big.
>> Yeah. Bro, we have student
>> they stay up
>> or they lose it.
>> Some some guys lose it. Yeah.
>> Because they don't have experience.
>> I've had students take a like it's been
their first three weeks of learning how
to trade. They've taken $1,000 to about
$130,000 the first three weeks.
>> Then they go crazy.
>> Yeah. They'll withdraw like a h 100red.
They'll leave like the 20 30 and then
they'll blow that because they they were
just like get too aggressive and get too
confident. But yeah,
>> and they get broke. They become broke
again.
>> I don't know if they become broke again,
but we've had students that have made a
lot, lost a lot, you know? So should
they what what's your advice? If if I'm
a student and I make a,000 or I have
a,000
>> but I'm broke though. a thousand. We get
up 100,000. What do I do? What's my next
play? But I don't have the experience. I
just got lucky.
>> Yeah. I I got a little bit of, you know,
knowledge from you, but I'm not there to
be going to buy a new car or
>> betting the 130. Like, what's my next
step?
>> I would withdraw half of that money.
Withdraw 50. Leave 50 in the account.
And then
>> withdraw 50 in
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Withdraw 50. Lock in
something in your bank, you know, like
pay off lock in the bank. Yeah. Lock
lock in some debt, pay off some debt,
whatever. Leave the 50 in the account.
Okay. Boom.
>> Keep going.
>> And then from that 50k in the account,
you only risk a small percentage per
trade. So you're not overexposing.
>> Also, don't bet the 50.
>> Don't bet the 50. No.
>> No. Don't bet.
>> Don't play like I'm broke. So
>> yeah. Yeah. The risk management is what
keeps you alive in this game.
>> Because if I don't have the experience,
I should be using that 50 to get the
experience.
>> Yeah.
>> But if I use that 50 and betting like I
have the experience, I don't have any
money to play with no more.
>> Yeah. You might lose the whole thing.
Correct. So when you get the experience,
then you can go in.
>> Yeah, you can go in. Correct.
>> So what is the rule? What percentage of
my stuff can I go in? If I got a million
dollars,
>> what percentage should I play? Cuz it's
going to be different. If I got a
thousand, okay, 20%,
you know what I'm saying? Million 20%.
>> I I have a $3 million account. I risk
four to 7% every trade.
>> Four to 7%.
>> Every trade. Yeah.
>> That's my risk appetite on my account.
>> You go like you can run out.
>> Yeah. No, I can never run out. I would
have to lose 30 trades in a row. That's
practically impossible.
>> Oh, really?
>> I I think it's impossible to lose more
than 15 trades in a row. If all of the
trades
>> Even if you suck.
>> Even if you suck. Yeah. I think it's
impossible
>> if Let me Let me be very clear here. If
every trade that you take has met the
strategy to perfection, if you're
following all these steps, cuz like if
the market is
>> so as good as you are, right, that now
you're good. rate like you're top 1%.
>> I would I would have say I'm like top
four or 5%. Yeah.
>> Okay. So, with the skill that you have,
is it guaranteed that you're going to be
up in 5 years or could you still just
have a bad 5 years?
>> I don't think I could ever have a bad 5
years. No,
>> you could have a bad year.
>> But when I say bad year, I mean you're
under like you lost money.
>> No, I don't think I can have a bad year.
>> You can't lose money at this point. You
can't like go 365 and lose money.
>> No, you could lose money in 30 days for
sure. in a year. Definitely not.
>> No,
>> no, no.
>> It's dead.
>> No, no, that that'll never happen.
>> So, you secure your lot.
>> You pretty much have salary. Like,
>> but yeah, like I can definitely be
negative for a quarter. Like, I've had
two month losing streaks, but a whole
whole year there's no way.
>> I don't want to say it's impossible. You
know, something might happen, but
there's a very
>> But them two months though, you you heat
it. You're like, "Yo, watch out."
>> Bro, I I've lost like I think it was it
was like 900 grand in a period of like
60 to 90 days. It was brutal. You were
pissed.
>> I mean, it was just loss after loss
after loss after last.
>> But you smiled during that time.
>> I did. Yeah, I smelled a lot.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it was all like
publicly like on social media [__] as
well, which is
>> But see, you definitely gained off of
losing. That's lit.
>> But you mean like
>> you gained off of losing? Like people
are just like, "Oh, did they know you
were down almost a mill?"
>> I mean, bro, people were losing with me.
Yeah. Like I was sharing the trick.
People make money with me and they also
lose with me.
>> Part of the game. Losing is very normal.
That's why you only risk a small. But
you knew that you were going to bounce
back and get out of that.
>> I Yeah, I knew.
>> You weren't like, "Yo, I'm about to be
done with this."
>> No, I mean, bro, it's just it's just a
pattern, you know, like if you you're
flipping a coin head or tails, you know,
10 hells tails can come out 10 times,
but it's a matter of time that heads
comes out.
>> The game is you just can't run out of
money to play with.
>> Correct. You can't overlever yourself.
That's what a lot of traders do. They
just are too aggressive with the risk
management.
>> So, if a heavy like if a dude came in
here just like with like the hugest ego
and just like he took over your body,
right? clone you. Whatever.
>> New Alex G. He still has skill, but now
he's just betting above his means.
>> He can go broke.
>> Yeah.
>> Have you ever thought about this stuff?
>> I swear to God, you're asking the best
questions ever, bro. Like, I'm not
>> Oh, cuz I want to see if I'm going to
play a game, I want to see the odds of
winning.
>> No, but like you're you're you're
literally asking the right questions
because you're asking a longevity
question. You're not You're not asking
how to get rich, you know? You're asking
how to stay in the game
>> 100%.
>> And this is a game of staying in the
game, you know? Like, you don't ever win
this game. This game doesn't end. Yeah.
The goal is to stay in as long as you
possibly can.
>> Yeah.
>> And the way you stay in as lo as long as
you possibly can is by having that risk
management.
>> Yeah.
>> Risk management is what keeps you in the
game.
>> Literally.
>> And that's why I got to see is it even a
game I want to play. But it seems like
if you're smart, you can keep running.
>> It's all about how you control your
decisions on when all of this. So I I
have a checklist, right?
>> And whenever I go enter a trade, I
literally check something off.
>> Yeah.
>> If it's there. So let's say I have I I
have I think it's 18 confluences before
I go enter a trade.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Let's say this I have this I
don't have this I don't have this I have
this I have
>> at that point I can make the decision
the executive decision being like you
know what [__] it I'm going to take the
trade
>> or like you know what I don't want to
take the trade. I'm going to wait until
everything is checked off.
>> That decision making to enter the trade
when things are checked off or not is
what's going to give you that longevity.
>> Okay. and how much I risk. If I want to
risk 5% of my account or if I'm going to
risk 50% of my account, that will be the
longevity of you in this game. The
decision making behind how many reasons
you need to enter the trade and what
you're going to risk. That's it.
>> Okay?
>> We're going to do a test later in the
future where we're going to get a random
like probably a homeless person from the
street and we're we're not going to
teach him how to trade at all. We're
just going to give him this and we're
going to give him a risk management.
Like we're gonna be like, "Brother, all
you could risk is 1%." He has to get a
hundred trades wrong in a row to blow
his account. That would never happen.
>> Yeah.
>> And I guarantee you that he will make
more money than an experienced trader
that would be risking
>> 50
>> 50%.
>> Really?
>> He just has to lose two trades
>> and he's done. Dang.
>> This person can trade 20 trades and he
won't be negative.
>> So you got to be you got to kind of like
slow grind it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's this is a business.
Yeah. Imagine trading as if it were to
be like your your physique. You know,
you're not going to get abs within the
first 24 hours of going to the gym.
Yeah.
>> It's a process. You need to
>> if I get under 400 lb on day one, I'm
gonna hurt myself and I'm going to be
out of the game forever.
>> Correct. Correct. Yeah.
>> Scarred for life.
>> Yeah. You need to f like if you're 400
lb, you need to lower your calories. You
can't just go and do 2hour cardio, 2
hour sauna. The next day you're not
going to want to go to the gym. You
won't like it. You do 15 minutes cardio,
15 minutes sauna. You slowly ease into
it and then over time you're going to
see the difference.
>> Then you become a big dog. Then you can,
you know, go hang with the wolves.
>> Correct. Same thing.
>> Rock with that.
>> All right. Cool. That was a good
sidetrack. I like that. I'm telling you
that that's very important that you have
like you're asking the perfect
questions, right?
>> Appreciate it.
>> So, back to the area of interest, right?
So, if a market is for example right
here, let's say bullish or bearish.
>> Uh, bearish. I mean bullish.
>> Correct. It went over that.
>> Yes. when I wrote this. So this is the
higher high. This is the higher low.
>> You need to look for the area of
interest
inside of this higher high and higher
low.
>> The market over here could have done
anything that it has wanted like this.
You don't care about up here. You don't
care about below here. You don't care
below the higher low. You don't care
above the higher high.
>> So right here you would start looking
left, right? So the market's going to
start retracing back.
>> Oh yeah. Right there.
>> Yeah. So the market's going to start
coming back. So, you put three in there
on purpose. Like, you know how to just
put three in there?
>> Like three touches?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, yeah. I'm just doing it for the
example. Yeah.
>> Okay. So, let's say that this didn't
exist, right?
>> Mhm.
>> The area of interest, could it be this
cuz it's kind of going down or no?
>> No. The area of interest always has to
be horizontal. Has to be a horizontal
line
>> or horizontal box.
>> So, that's too low.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> It have to be horizont.
>> So, there would be no area of interest
if that wasn't there.
>> One, two, wouldn't be no area. Well, te
technically if if this wasn't here, this
market would be bearish. So, we'd have
to be looking for an area of interest to
sell.
>> Mhm.
>> Cuz lower this is the lower high. This
is a lower low. This right here that
does not have three touches. This does
not have three touches.
>> Yeah. It would be none.
>> There's no area of interest. Okay.
>> Correct. If there's no three touches,
there's no area of interest.
>> Okay.
>> Right.
>> Perfect.
>> So, if there's no area of interest, you
just don't don't do nothing.
>> You just don't take the trade. Really?
That's
>> Some people still take the trade.
>> That's the problem as well. Yeah,
>> but that
>> they just bored.
>> Exactly. That's what I'm saying. Like
people will literally
>> That would be me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'll be like, "Brother, listen. We got
to do something."
>> Yeah. That's what I'm saying. Like
people will have the trend. So like for
example, they'll be able to identify
that the market's bearish, but they
won't have an area of interest.
>> Slow motion is no motion.
>> Yeah. Oh, I mean, yeah, but like they
won't risky.
>> Yeah. They won't have an area of
interest. And you're like, you know
what? F it. We're still going to send
it. And it's like, well, now you're just
taking a high risk trade.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do it all the time.
[laughter]
>> But but the beauty of it is that I know
what I am entering. Like I'm I'm fully
aware of it.
>> Yeah. I'm I'm aware of it and like I'm
I'm ready for the risk and like I'm I'm
going to go out to the ocean. I see a
wave and I see a fin.
>> Might be a shark. It might be a dolphin.
But you know what my experience tells
>> sometimes that game is better to play
anyways.
>> Yeah. The day is sunny. There's
beautiful waves. The current
everything's good. Is it worth the risk
or not? Depends what you're asking.
>> Yeah. And then you get better when you
get the area of interest because that's
cake to you now.
>> Correct.
>> Because you're taking in big waves.
>> Correct. Correct. All right.
Perfect. So, let's set uh one more
example here when it comes to the area
of interest. So,
>> I thought we was going to press a couple
buttons.
>> There's so much more you need to learn
before that.
>> It's different.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like, you need
to know why you're pressing the button.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. So, this market is bullish.
Higher high, higher low. Now, this
market, we're anticipating that it's
going to have a retracement to buy. Is
that an area of interest? Yes or no?
>> No.
>> Perfect. Is that an area of interest?
Yes or no?
>> Yes. One, two, three. Is this an area of
interest?
>> No.
>> Oh, yes. One, two, three.
>> It is.
>> Oh, area of interest. No, cuz it's below
the uh
>> Yes.
>> on fire. Perfect. That was that was a
trick question. So, technically that is
an area of interest, but just not for
this specific trade we're interested in
right now. Right. So, we would be
waiting for this market to have a
retracement into this area of interest
right here. Let me put this waiting for
this market to have an retracement into
this area of interest where it's
rejected once, twice, three times. Now,
can the market have a reaction from here
and have a push up? Of course.
>> Can the market break below this area of
interest and then have a push up? Of
course.
>> But that is just simply not our trade.
>> Okay?
>> We just simply didn't meet our strategy.
we move on to the next trade.
>> Right? So once the trade makes it to
this area of interest, what do you do?
>> You bet.
>> You need to have the next point, entry
signal. The most important thing
>> going to tell you that the trade is
ready to enter. So let's summarize
before we get into entry signal.
>> So right when we hit right here, it's
time to bet. We going we gonna be
>> But we need to have our entry signal. We
need to have the indication that it's
ready to enter. Just because it's there
doesn't mean that you could enter it
right away.
>> Okay.
>> Perfect example is you have a but that
wait that if this is our area of
interest
>> Mhm.
>> are we're betting that it's going down,
right?
>> No. No. Cuz we're we're bullish once it
gets there. We're going to bet that it's
going to go up.
>> So bullish. Okay. So if we got the area
of interest and we're bullish, we're
going up.
>> Correct.
>> Always. If we're bearish, we're going
down.
>> And we're at an area of interest, we're
going down. Yes. Always.
>> Because we're up right now. Okay.
Silent.
>> Correct. So to summarize, area of
interest is something that is consisted
of three touches.
>> If you are below the resistance, this is
considered the ceiling. That is the
roof.
>> If you are above, it is considered the
support. For example, let's
>> set this example right here. That is the
support. It's going to be the floor.
>> These combined resistance and support
combined is the area of interest.
>> Yeah. Three or more touches is what
validates it. Whether you have
resistance as the three taps, whether
you have support as the three taps or
whether it's a hybrid where you have one
resistance, one support and one
resistance. As long as this zone has
three taps that
>> perfect, right? So this is area of
interest. Now when a trade is bullish,
we need to wait for price to come to
that area of interest. Once price is at
that area of interest, then we move on
to potentially entering the trade. So,
next point and technically the final
point is going to be entry signal.
So, entry signal is I'm going to set
another example. It's almost Have you
ever played baseball?
>> Yeah.
>> You play baseball, right? Okay. So, you
know when you have the batter, right?
Don't mind my stick figure. M
>> you know the pitcher that is going to be
pitching you the ball from this area
over here. This ball that he's going to
be pitching at you, it needs to land for
you to swing at it within that box.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, if the ball doesn't land
within that box, it's a foul ball. If it
lands up here or over here, right?
>> Your job as a baseball player with the
bat is to hit this ball in this zone for
you to either get a home run or for you
to actually hit it.
>> Yeah. Now, many times these baseball
pitchers make it seem tricky and right
before it hits the box, it drops off or
it might get out of the box and that's
where you see these baseball players
swinging to miss. Right. Your job as a
baseball pitcher, I mean as a as a
batter is to hit the perfect ball.
>> Yeah.
>> Imagine that you are in a game of
baseball and your only job is to bat and
swing at the perfect ball. the pitcher
is just going to be throwing balls every
single second of the day. Your ball is
your job is just to wait for the right
one. You cannot humanly possibly swing
at every single ball is going to come.
You're going to strike out. You're going
to get tired and you're just not going
to be in the game long enough.
>> Facts.
>> Need to wait for that perfect pitch. And
that perfect pitch is when you're inside
of that box. There might be many times
where you're looking at that ball and it
might seem like it's going to go into
the box. And if for whatever reason you
don't have the perfect indication to
enter it or to swing at it, you don't
have to.
>> You're not obligated to swing at it
anymore.
>> Miss a good
>> Yeah.
>> A good ball. It's it's okay.
>> It's it's totally fine, right? You're
not going to get stried out. Nothing's
going to happen. That's the exact same
thing when it comes to trading and the
entry signal. So, whenever the market is
trending, right? Let's just pretend like
this is an area of interest and price
comes back into this area of interest.
So now we're here going to be looking
for our entry signal. Many traders look
to have any possible reason to enter the
trade and that's completely wrong. You
shouldn't just enter the trade for any
reason just because a trade is at the
area of interest. You should not enter
just because the ball that the pitcher
is pitching at you. You don't have to
swing at it just because it's right dead
in the center. Can you? Sure. But you
want to make sure that it is perfect,
that the lights align, that the wind
aligns, that everything is good. You
don't have to swing at it.
>> Now, this entry signal needs to be
perfect every single time for you to
take the trade. It's okay to miss a
trade. Can you sometimes be too picky or
it wait for too many confirmation and
you miss it? Sure.
>> So, if you're trading, you need to trade
every day as long as the market is open.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And you need to wait for the
perfect entry for the perfect trade.
>> Correct.
>> Can you miss a day?
>> Yeah, you can miss a day. There's no
problem. You can miss a day playing
baseball. Nothing's going to happen.
>> Oh, really? You might miss a week.
>> You might miss opportunities, but the
opportunities are like the pitcher is
always going to be there pitching the
ball. It's a machine.
>> You trade every day.
>> I'm looking at the markets every day for
a trade.
>> But you might not trade every day.
>> I might not trade every day.
>> Oh, really?
>> I might take two trades a week, Max.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, not everybody trades every day.
>> No, there's some traders that take four
or five trades a day, but you're you're
basically being more exposed to losing.
The more you trade, the more odds you
have of losing. The more swings that you
take, the more odds you have of missing
and striking out.
>> I try.
>> Don't you get better, though?
>> No.
>> Really?
>> It's about quality, not quantity.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. It's about waiting for that
perfect ball. You don't need to switch.
You don't need to swing at every pitch,
>> bro.
>> At the point that I am right now in my
journey.
>> So, you would put content different
though. Content is like more It's a
little bit of both.
>> Yeah. No, content is a volume game.
>> It's volume game
>> because you're competing against
>> you're going to get better and then one
of them might hit.
>> Yes. Correct. This is Yeah. So it's not
in trading it's different.
>> Yeah. Cuz like the problem with content
is that you're in control.
>> You know, like whatever you put out
there is what you're going to get.
>> You don't control the market at all.
[laughter]
>> You know, you can't control this.
>> Don't bring that to this market.
>> Do not bring that.
>> You will be in trouble.
>> You could you could, you know, get
experience by trading a lot more and,
you know, swinging at every pitch, but
you're going to get tired. I can almost
guarantee you. Like you you will cap
out,
>> right? So once a trade is at an area of
interest, you want to wait for an entry
signal. So the first thing that you can
have is going to be a rejection candle
or you can have a engulfing candle.
>> Yeah.
>> Have you ever heard of these before?
>> Nope.
>> Okay. So a reject what's a rejection?
>> She said no.
>> Correct. A rejection is when something
gets rejected.
>> Yeah.
>> When something is engulfing what's an
engulfing? Get ready.
>> It's when something engulfs something.
>> Yeah. Like right now like you are
engulfing me in size. Like look look at
the camera like just like like you see
like you are bigger than
>> close bro. No, we're not that much
[laughter] of a difference though.
>> But like but like you are far bigger
than I am, right? Like you are engulfing
me, right?
>> So rejecting is when something is
literally rejecting it. Engulfing is
when something is eating something.
>> So you're going to look at this in forms
of candlesticks. So you see these boxes
that go up and down in the markets,
right? These are the candlesticks. These
are just how the market is reflecting
price. It's very similar. So basically,
you would have a market that is like
this, but instead of it being a line
chart, it's going to be in a candlestick
chart. So it's the exact same market.
It's just being reflected
in these candlesticks like this. Right?
So this market right here is literally
the same market as this one right here.
It's just being reflected in these
candlesticks, right? These things up and
down. So when you have one of these
candlesticks for example, let's say this
is the area of interest. This is the
box. So we're basically zooming in at
this right here right now
>> in candlesticks.
>> If the next candlestick has a big wick,
so this wick is a rejection. That's
basically the trail of price and you
have like a cross something like this, a
big cross that is a rejection. That is
the market letting you know that we are
rejecting this market. Or you can have
what is called an engulfing market.
Right? So this right here once again
we're at this area of interest. Price is
now officially here. We're basically
zooming in here. And the next candle
would be an engulfing candlestick. So
it's clearly showing that this candle is
bigger than these two.
>> It can be bigger than one, two, three.
The more the better. So this is a sign
of rejection because clearly we've
pushed up very strong from here or this
is another very strong sign because
price went below it but closed above it.
So it's showing that it's not liking
this area anymore. So this right here is
a rejection candle and then this right
here is an engulfing candle. So once
price makes it into this area and we
either have a cross or a bullish candle,
we're basically ready now to enter the
trade.
>> That is our entry signal. So our entry
signal could be to take it now or you
say, you know what, I'm not feeling it
or you know what, I want for it to
retest it again or I want it to have
another engulfing candlestick. At that
point, you can get as picky as you want,
right? You can ask for as many things,
but this is officially the green light
for you to take this trade. This is
officially the pitcher has pitched you a
straight ball into your box. You're
standing right here. You've been waiting
all day with your bat. It's perfectly
dead in the center. The speed is not too
fast. It's not a 100 mile per hour ball.
It's a 60 mph ball. It's a straight
ball. It's ready to swing.
>> Mhm.
>> You can make the decision to swing or
not. At that point is entirely up to you
and your experience.
>> That is entry signal.
>> It's very simple. It's just consisted of
a rejection candlestick or an engulfing
candlestick.
>> Does that make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> Might make more sense now when we go to
the actual charts and we quiz.
>> Once you get one of these, you're you're
ready to swing.
>> Correct. You're basically ready to swing
into the market.
>> You don't have to, but
>> Yeah. Correct. Okay. So, I'm going to
set an example. Right. So, for example,
this market right here, right? Let's
just do it like
like this.
Bullish or bearish.
Uh bullish.
>> Correct. Now,
>> is that trade ready to enter? Yes or no?
>> Yes.
>> Where's your entry signal?
>> What candlestick is that?
>> H What candlestick is that? We're
looking for a rejection one. Um,
>> it's the uh rejection.
>> This is a rejection counter. That's a
cross, right? That right there is not a
cross. It's not a rejection count.
>> Okay. So, you're talking about how the
it looks.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> So, if you would to put a cross. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> I was saying rejection cuz it's going
down.
>> No, but it's off the look.
>> Correct. Yeah. Yeah. It's off. So, it'll
show you. You don't have to like
>> No, you don't have to you don't have to
second guess it. It'll it'll literally
tell you whether it's a rejection candle
or whether it's an engulfing candle.
>> Oh yeah.
>> So right now you don't have
>> engulfing.
>> Yeah. No, this is not an engulfing. This
is basically here. The engulfing would
be this candle right here. That
>> making it bigger.
>> Yeah. It's where it eats the last
candle.
>> Okay. So
>> So why would it do that?
>> Because that is showing that it's price
is rejecting the area of interest since
we're above it.
>> Okay. Because whenever whenever we're
below it, we're rejecting it down.
Whenever we're above it, we're rejecting
it to the upside.
>> Okay?
>> So that right there would be a rejection
candle to the upside. That is our entry
signal.
>> Okay?
>> Another example would be if price
basically is at this area of interest,
right? This area of interest and then we
have a cross that
>> is another rejection candle. That is our
ready to enter this trade to the upside.
But being that we didn't have either one
of those, we're not ready.
>> Correct. When I asked you, it was like
this.
>> We had we did not have neither of those.
So, we were not ready to take this
trade.
>> I was thinking we're ready cuz we have a
common area.
>> Yeah. The area of interest.
>> Yeah. That is where you would need to
wait for one of these.
>> Okay.
>> For you to enter the trade.
>> Okay. So, it doesn't matter about the
area of interest. You need to see
rejection or engulfing.
>> Correct.
>> Okay. That's perfect. Yeah. You need to
wait for either or to happen.
>> Okay. It could be like four or five
different spots of area of interest.
Correct.
>> Correct. Okay. Correct.
>> Still wait.
>> Yeah. You still have to wait. Correct.
>> Okay.
>> Correct.
>> And the the charts will show you
rejection, engulfing all the time.
>> It it'll literally give you one of these
two tell you.
>> Well, it it'll show you many other ones,
but you only look for these two right
here. A rejection or an engulfing. Okay.
>> Let's go to the charts and let's see how
good you learn. All right. So, I'm going
to show you an example now on the actual
chart. So I was showing you this earlier
was on the line chart which is something
like this right? So we don't really
trade on the line chart. The line chart
is used to identify market structure
something is bullish or if something is
bearish right but we actually trade on
the candlestick chart which are these
lines that go up or down. Right? So just
to show you an example of what that
rejection candle looks like. This would
be it right there. See that cross that
happened there perfectly. The one next
to it actually would be a perfect
example of an engulfing candlestick.
This right over here would be an example
of a engulfing candlestick as well. This
right here would be example of that
cross of that rejection.
>> This over here would be that example of
a engulfing. Let me grab this right
here.
>> So cross.
>> Correct. Yes. Yes. Correct.
>> Enguling.
>> Correct. So this would be a cross.
Massive engulfing.
>> Wait, where's the cross? So, I guess you
can consider one of these two right here
cross.
>> Wow.
>> Because it's a it's a I mean, the body
is a bit big. It would be better if it
was like this one right here where it
would have no body. So, it was it's just
like a little cross. The candlestick
isn't ready.
>> I was going to see a cross right here.
>> Correct. Yeah. It's not It's not It's
not the cleanest cross. Yeah. This one
ain't bad on that one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Correct. Exactly. So, like
if it's not clean, you don't have to
take it.
>> That's a cross.
>> Very clear cross.
>> This is an engulfing candlestick to the
downside. This is not an engulfing. Oh,
you're saying this blue one is across
>> kind of. It's a
>> It's just not like thin.
>> Correct. Correct. It's It's not The body
isn't thin. Correct.
>> This right here is a very clear one. You
can tell there's literally nothing
there.
>> It's just a cross.
>> And you know, we can go on for literally
ages just finding these.
>> This is not the cleanest cross, but some
somehow there.
>> So, it's never always going to be
perfect. You just want to have it as
perfect as you possibly can ask for,
>> right? So this is how we look at the
markets when it comes to actual market
structure. It's going to be based off of
just these candlestick moves, right? So
let me ask you, is this market bullish
or is this market bearish?
>> Uh it's
bullish.
>> Bullish. Okay. Where's the higher high?
Is the higher high at point number one
or at point number two?
>> The one.
>> Correct.
So this would be the higher high. We're
going to write down here.
Higher high. All right. Now, where's the
higher low? Is the higher low at point
number one
or at point number two?
>> Two. All right. Perfect. On the money.
Yes. So this market is indeed bullish.
So this is the higher high and this is
the higher low. Right. So we're going to
put here higher low. So, we know that
this market is bullish
>> and we know that we're going to only
look for the area of interest within
this higher high and this higher low
>> thousand%.
>> Okay. So, we start working our way down.
Obviously, we're not going to look for
an area of interest up here because
price
>> found it already.
>> Yeah. Where is it?
>> A lot.
>> Where is it?
Okay. All right. Let's see. We bring it
all the way down here. This one. Right
there.
>> Mhm.
>> Bang. Correct. That's an area of
interest. You see it? one. So, we'll
circle it off, right? So, we got one,
we got two, and then we got three. Area
of interest. But there's also another
area of interest, which would be
somewhat this one or this wouldn't be
considered an area of interest, but here
you have one and two. So, it's not
considered an area of interest. This is
the only area of interest.
>> Easy. That's it. This is not an area of
interest. This is not an area of
interest. Right? Everything makes sense
so far, right?
>> 100%.
>> So, you can tell that the market is
bullish. You can tell what is what,
right?
>> Now, what if I told you that this market
right here is exactly what you just did
right now, just you did it on the line
chart and here is on the candlestick
chart.
>> So, if you notice, it's literally the
same market,
>> but just more confusing.
>> No, it's [laughter]
it's not confusing. It's just in a much
it's presented in a different format.
>> So, correct, correct, correct. These are
all those structure points right there.
So I was teaching you in English, right?
So you just learned how to read and
write in English.
>> Oh, that's Europe.
>> Yes. This is this is USDCHF. No, but
what I'm saying is like the language
that you learned market structure is in
English right here.
>> English.
>> Now this is Chinese.
>> Oh, really?
>> But we're saying the same thing. This is
saying
>> this is actually in Chinese.
>> I mean, kind of. Yeah, something like
that. No, it's not actually in Chinese.
Well, I mean, they're actually called
the Chinese candlesticks. I mean, I'm
sorry, Japanese candlesticks.
Yeah, these are Japanese candlestick,
right? So, this says the same sentence.
So, this is basically explaining this
market is bullish. We are at a higher
high, higher low, and we're at an area
of interest. That is what this says in
English.
>> Yeah.
>> Now, this is this is saying the same
thing but in Japanese, and you're
reading it off of the candlesticks. So,
where are let's say that this is the
area of interest?
Are we ready to enter this trade based
off of our entry signal? Yes or no?
Forget about this.
Are we ready to enter this trade based
off of the entry signal? The entry
signal, remember?
>> Uh entry signal. Uh
>> so this is where price is. This is the
area of interest that you just marked
off.
>> Yeah.
Let me see that real quick one more
time.
>> No.
>> Why?
Cuz this isn't a cross, right? Correct.
Come on, man.
>> That's it. That's literally it.
>> That is not a cross. So, there's no
rejection. And then there is So, you
don't have one of these right here. If
you had something like this, if you had
a cross that was presented right here at
this area of interest, you going in.
>> You would be ready to go in. Or
>> if you had one of these candlestick,
>> if you had an engulfing candlestick like
that, you would go. But you Yeah. But
you don't have neither. So, you don't
take the trade.
>> That's trading. I'm ready.
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> I'm telling you, I'm ready.
>> All right. So, right now, you have three
tries. I'm going to go back. I'm going
to find an opportunity and then you
either decide if you want to enter or
not.
>> If you get all three of them wrong, you
eat this chip.
>> Ain't no way.
>> All you got to do is get one right.
>> You taught me too much, man. I wanted to
see I want the people to see me eat the
chip.
>> All right. So, you got to trick me.
>> Yeah, I'm going to trick your eyes. So,
you got like you got to like
[clears throat] turn around, right? So,
let me see.
>> So, you first start off with the line
chart. Is this market bullish or is it
bearish?
>> Bullish.
>> Okay. Where's the higher high? Where's
the higher low?
>> Higher high is right there.
>> Okay.
>> So, higher low right there.
>> Okay. Perfect. Higher high. Higher low.
All right. Now, what?
>> Now, we got to see if we're going Oh, we
got to find the uh
>> area of interest.
>> Area of interest.
>> All right. So, is the area of interest
like this? We look for it like this.
>> Bring it up.
>> Correct. Bring it up. All right.
Perfect. So, we're start working our way
down. is a
>> I see an area of interest.
>> You see it?
>> Is this an area of interest?
>> We can count it off, right? All right.
We have one,
two,
>> three.
>> Yeah.
>> Four.
>> Valid area of interest.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. So, we're at an area of interest.
So, what do we do now? We go to the
candlesticks and we look better.
>> Yeah. All right. So that is exactly
>> I'm bet.
>> What is happening right here?
>> What are you going to do?
>> I'm betting.
>> You're going to buy or sell?
>> I'm buying.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm selling.
>> You sure?
>> Wait, let me see.
[laughter]
>> Very easy to click. Yeah.
>> Oh, wait. All right. So, yeah. Uh,
>> the market's bullish and you're at a
support level.
>> Oh, this is a hard bar. Hold on. So,
we're bullish.
I'm saying so we're going up. So, I'mma
buy.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, if you're bullish and you're
at a support, it makes sense to buy. You
sure?
>> 100%.
>> You sure?
>> Thousand%.
>> Okay. All right. So, you're ready to buy
this trade right here?
>> He's trying to trick me. Chat, come on.
>> Are you ready to buy this trade right
here?
>> Wait, hold on.
>> Remember, you need
>> No, no, no. I'm not buying because I had
a cross.
>> Yeah, you need the rejection at the area
of interest. This is an area of
interest. That's your cross.
>> So, that's good.
>> Yes. Okay.
>> So, you ready to buy or sell?
>> Buy.
>> You sure?
>> You sure if you
>> I'm ready to buy. All right.
>> He trying to trick me, bro.
>> All right. Look. Three.
>> Is it going to say it?
>> Yeah. Right now, we're about to find
out. Three, two, one. Bang. You're
right.
>> I'm out.
>> You got me.
>> Okay. But you
>> did you know already?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Oh, yeah. [laughter]
>> Yeah. I I went back and I found Okay,
but like you're seeing the importance of
it's the same things that I've been
teaching you.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> I look for the
>> because it was bullish. You have to buy
when it's bullish.
>> Yeah, you buy when it's bullish. You buy
the support and you have the rejection
and that's it. Trade goes up.
>> Okay. Really? What if I had the uh the
candlestick, the big one,
>> the engulfing? Same thing. Look,
>> still on buying.
>> Yeah. Correct. If you see here, that's
the engulfing. You could have still
entered off of the engulfing, for
example.
>> And I'm only buying cuz it's bullish.
>> Yes.
>> So, I know it already.
>> Correct. I'm I'm an expert.
>> Yeah. No, you're not an expert. Yeah,
you're getting [laughter] there. But
that that was really good. That was
really good for your first time. All
right. Let me find you another example.
All right. Right now, you're one zip.
So, you're up right now.
>> All right, let me find you another
example. So, for example, this market
right here, I'm going to assist you once
again. I'm going to give you this little
help right here.
>> Yeah,
>> this little market structure help. All
right. So, is this market
bullish or is this market bearish?
>> Bullish.
>> Okay. Where's the higher high and higher
low? One.
>> Higher high.
>> And two. You sure? The higher high is
number two.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Higher high is number one or number two?
>> Two.
>> Yeah. I was trying to trick you, but you
[laughter]
>> Yeah. Higher high is number two, right?
>> Yes. Correct.
>> And then the higher low is this.
>> No, the higher low would be this.
>> Yeah. So, right now we're bullish,
right? So, we would put our area of
interest and we would start working our
way down. And then boom, what do we have
here? We have
>> high area of interest.
>> Yep. We have one,
>> two, three,
>> one
right here. Two, and we have three.
>> Yeah.
>> So, we're bullish and we're at a valid
area of interest, right?
>> Okay, cool.
This is where we are right now with
price. What do we have here? So, if
we're bullish on an area of interest,
all we need is our entry signal. Our
entry signal is either a rejection or an
engulfing. What do we have here?
>> Engulfing.
>> Where is it?
>> Is that an the point is at the bottom?
>> I don't know. It's okay to make a
mistake. [laughter]
>> No, it ain't.
>> Uh, it's right there.
>> So, you're saying the current candle is
an engulfing. That means you're ready to
enter the trade off of the area of
interest when it's bullish.
>> [snorts]
>> Dad,
>> it's okay to be wrong.
>> No, I ain't going to answer that one.
>> You don't want to answer this one?
>> No.
>> Okay, that is actually a great decision
that you can make. That That's a great
decision.
>> I'm not sure on it.
>> Yeah. Yo, bro. Dude, that's [__]
amazing, bro. Yo, I'm not kidding.
>> You got me a lot, dude.
>> I'm telling you, I'm not kidding. Like
99% of people will be like, "You know
what? F it. I'm just going to jump in
it. You know,
>> the other one I was sure on. This one
>> you're not sure on. Okay, cool. But if
you would do something, what would you
do?
>> Cuz you can you can just hypothetically
still predict the market. You don't have
to enter. What would you do?
>> If I had to do something.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm see. So, we're bullish right now.
>> Mhm.
>> One, two, three.
>> Correct. This would be
>> Yeah. I'm I'm betting that it's going
up.
>> You would bet that it goes up.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
And this would be the rejection here.
Okay. So, you would bet that would go
up. You'd put something like this.
>> All right. Well, guess what?
>> It's going. Oh,
>> up. It went up.
>> So, you just missed out on some money.
>> So, what would you you would have bet on
it?
>> Yeah, I would have bought. Correct.
>> Because the candle.
>> Yes. Correct. That would
>> is a candle.
>> Yes, that's a bullish engulfing candle.
>> So, why I thought it had the point had
to be taller.
>> It it is that that candle at that point
right there did engulf these last two
candles. M.
>> So yes, that right there would have
counted 100%.
>> Okay. So the So the candle doesn't have
to be like this and then have the point
at the top.
>> No, it doesn't.
>> Cuz I'm thinking of seeing the big point
at the bottom.
>> The wick. No, it doesn't need that.
>> It doesn't matter about the weight.
>> No. No.
>> So what's the W? The wick is just
>> It's just like the trail of price. Just
a rejection.
>> So that's an engulfing candle to
>> correct. Yes. That's Yes. Correct. I'm
telling you that that was a great
decision. Like not taking the trade is a
great decision.
>> And I still learn like
>> you still learn. Correct.
>> So I I'll give you that one as well cuz
you're right about the trend. That's
two.
>> All right, third one. Let's see what's
going to happen. You're doing pretty
good. Like
>> I didn't think I was going to like I
didn't one. I didn't think it was this
complex,
>> but it's it's not comp or do you see
still see a comp?
>> Well, no, you have to sit down. It's not
hard.
>> Mhm.
>> You just got to sit down. If you watch
this video and you lock in, it's over.
Probably watch this video like twice.
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> It's over.
>> Yeah. You just need to get experience
learning the patterns. Correct.
>> Yeah.
>> So, here I'm going to hook you up once
again. Is this market bullish or is this
market bearish? Remember that's the
first thing you always have to identify
the trend.
>> Oh yeah. Is uh damn is confusing. Be I
mean bullish.
>> Bullish. Okay. Where's the higher high?
One or number two?
>> Two.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah. All right. Yeah.
>> Okay. Where's the higher low? one
or or two or one.
One.
>> Okay.
Correct. So price has not broken below
the higher low which still makes it
bullish.
>> Perfect.
>> So now we almost there. Almost.
>> Correct. Correct. It was almost there.
Yeah. This is like you know that's
exactly it.
>> So right now let's see are we at an area
of interest? Yes or no?
You said do we have an area of interest?
>> Yeah.
>> Correct. We have one,
two,
>> three,
>> three. And then I would also count this
structure here right here.
>> Oh, you count them. Okay.
>> So I would count them. Yeah. So we have
four.
>> So if you notice that is exactly what
this market is doing right here. It's
the same exact market,
>> right? So right now we're at that area
of interest.
>> Dang. So not saying that is definitely a
lot harder.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So,
>> put it in English.
>> Yeah.
>> Would you enter this trade at this area
of interest or no? Do you have your
entry signal or not?
>> Dang, it's hard again.
>> But yeah, I got it.
>> You would enter it? It's okay to be
wrong.
>> No, I wouldn't enter it.
>> You would not enter it. But what do you
think it's going to do? Go up or down?
>> Um,
it's going to go up.
>> It's going to go up. Mhm.
>> So you would not enter this position.
You sure? You're at an area. So look,
you're bullish. You're at an area of
interest and you have your rejection
entry
cross.
>> Oh, that's the cross.
>> Yes, that's the cross.
>> So it doesn't matter about the last one.
>> No, it just as long as you have that
cross there.
>> Oh, yeah, for sure. Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> You would you would enter it.
>> Is this This is not engulfing, is it?
>> No, that's not engulfing.
>> Okay. Even though it's a little bit
bigger than that. What? What makes it?
This is engulfing.
>> No. No. This one right here would be
engulfing cuz it ate the last two
candles. This one did not.
>> Oh, it's about the last two candles.
>> Yeah, we have to eat the last one.
>> So, this one ate that one, but So, if we
had two of these is engulfing.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, okay. I'm tripping. All right. Yeah.
So, but it doesn't matter about the last
one. If we see a cross,
>> it's good. Yeah.
>> What if the cross was right here?
>> Well, then the trade is it's been
missed. You know, you have to you have
to treat it live for
>> live for right now. Yeah.
>> But this is a second one.
>> That's fine. But that's where price is
right now. Live. Yeah,
>> but the price is right here though.
>> Yeah, but that's like right next to like
it's uh
>> What about the crosses right here? The
third one.
>> Well, that third candle didn't have a
cross made. So, you would have to wait
for the cross to be made.
>> Oh, yeah. So, if this one right here
>> Yeah. If you would be right here, no.
Cuz there's no cross here. You have a
cross. Yes. And after it's like another
confirmation, so it's good.
>> Okay. All right.
>> So, you would enter this trade just like
this.
>> Yeah. I'm enter.
>> All right. So this is where I didn't
teach you this but it's okay because you
know there there's always continuation
and learning but your stop-loss
placement is very very important.
>> Wherever you place your stop loss is
where you want to get out if the market
for whatever reason goes to that area.
>> So it automatically takes you out at
your pre-calculated risk and your take
profit is where it gets you out of your
profit. Let's say you would enter this
trade just like this. this price, for
example, hit your stop loss and it would
have taken you out, but it would have
still gone to your takerit. But because
your stop loss was too tight, you
basically lost the trade,
>> but you were right about the direction.
So, a lot of people, they do this, they
make the stop loss too tight, and they
don't give their trade breathing room.
They have to give their trade some
breathing room so the trade can breathe
before it gets to the ground.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Yeah. So, you could be right about the
direction, but the specific point where
you enter
>> Yeah. is important.
>> Yeah. Might be you have to give it some
breathing room.
>> Okay.
>> So, technically
>> have a lot of leverage.
>> Yeah. So, you were right here about the
direction of the move,
>> but your stop loss needed to be slightly
adjusted. I didn't teach you this, which
is totally fine. It's just
>> how do I know that it needs to be
slightly adjusted?
>> That is based off of how how big your
area of interest is, how big this
rejection is. Like, you know, we'll
calculate it with some tools that we
have and then it'll tell you, you know,
your stop loss should be here. Your stop
loss.
>> So, the area of rejection was not big
enough.
uh your stop loss was not big enough.
>> What's the stop loss?
>> It's where it's the pre-calculated
loss before you take the trade.
>> So this this right here it's fine.
You're what matters here is that you
once if you understand the direction of
the market
>> how you place your stop loss where
that's all very like that's like the
final part you know that's like so like
right now here think about it as you
know you're you're getting the swing now
you're not knowing if you run to first
base or second base first. Yeah. You
know, you're going to figure out you got
to go to first base first every time.
>> This is the same thing. All that matters
is that you could hit the ball.
>> We're still swinging.
>> Yeah. And that you know that you're
hitting it perfect.
>> Yeah.
>> So, in this example, you would be right
again, but you could have taken a loss
if your stop loss was placed
>> because it went down. Yeah.
>> So, technically one for two or
>> two. Yeah. Not bad. Not bad.
>> Not bad.
>> Yeah.
>> Technically, technically
>> technically technically technically. So,
I mean, yeah, that that's pretty much
what trading consists of. Trading
consists of let me just close it like
this. So trading pretty much consists of
trend.
>> Yeah.
>> Direction of the market consists of area
of interest which is where you're
interested in buying or selling and then
your entry signal.
>> Okay.
>> Does this make trading simpler to you?
How does it feel now?
>> Thousand%.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I feel like if I did this for at
least a week
>> Mhm.
>> And if I if I liked it,
>> you know what I'm saying? Which I kind
of do. I like to win period. So, if I
was watching these videos for like a
week, I feel like I could learn how to
trade.
>> I feel like I would be confident. I
probably would be too confident.
[laughter]
>> I'll probably go in and try to be the
next Alex G.
>> I mean I mean you could I'm telling you
the most important thing is your
decision.
>> I probably would watch this like while
I'm eating.
>> You could
>> or some like
>> See, but like that's
>> while I'm eating I'll just sit down and
pop a video up and just watch the trade.
>> Correct.
>> And then a week later I'm like 10k in.
>> Yeah. Correct. At least. Well, that's
the beauty of the Forex market because
it's open 24 to 55. So, you can do it at
any point throughout the day. If you're
if you're let's say you're working a 9
to5,
>> you have more time to get better.
>> Yeah. And you have more the market's
open for more opportunity.
>> Stock is not for you.
>> It's 9 to5. Let's say you get home at 5
from your 9 to 5. You can't do anything.
>> Dang.
>> But the other way around, the Forex
market, you could you could get home
from work at 5 and you can still trade
all night if you wanted to.
>> That's why the Forex is better.
>> Much better. Yeah.
>> Cuz you it doesn't sleep.
>> Correct. Yeah. other than weekends and
then weekends anyway,
>> which is better the rest. Yeah.
>> Dang.
>> Yeah. So, I mean, yeah, ju just to
summarize everything, everything just
really comes down to trend, area of
interest, and then the entry signal. Can
you take a trade without all of those
three lining up? Sure. It's just a
higher risk trade. Can you swing? Can
you get on the wave if it's raining and
there's sharks in the water? Can you
still surf a wave? Can you still catch
one? Sure. Just a bit higher risk. You
might get struck by thunder. You might
get eaten by a shark. That's all up to
that person's risk appetite and what
they want to do. Yeah.
>> What matters is that you understand that
you're at risk, that you're not naive or
you're clueless to it. That's the
problem with 99% of traders. They're
going in to go surf when it's
sharkinfested waters and the weather is
terrible,
>> brother. Relax.
>> What?
>> No, I'm saying they need to relax.
>> Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Correct. They they just need to
chill. Like, you're not forced to go
surf 24/7. You need to wait for the
right opportunity.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> you want to eat the chip?
>> Come on. [laughter] They were like
shack.
>> You really You really want to eat the
chip?
>> Where's the chip, bro?
>> Oh my god.
>> It is a chip. So, we're here with Ashton
Haw and he says that you can eat this
hot chip. This is the world's hottest
chip.
>> Easy.
>> All right, brother. If you could eat the
whole chip and not ask for water for 60
seconds, they'll give you $1,000. Cash.
Easy.
Brother, you're you're cooked,
[laughter] brother. You're cooked, bro.
Is it hot? [clears throat]
[laughter]
Is it hot?
>> I know.
Wait, [clears throat] you're going to
eat the other half?
>> You can't tell. It's a [cough]
>> Wait, you're going to Wait, you don't
have to eat the other half.
Where we at?
>> 25 seconds. Yo, you idiot, [laughter]
bro. This guy is out of his mind.
>> I had to compete.
>> Yo, how hot, brother? How is it?
>> I think you just can't talk.
>> No, but is it hot? Like, one out of 10.
One out of 10. What do you give it?
>> It's the hottest thing I had before.
>> Yeah.
Like, would you throw this on some tacos
or something?
>> No. [laughter]
>> Oh, I feel my heart. Oh my god, it's
worse now. It was chilling first.
>> Yeah,
>> when we're walking outside, it's going
to be a problem. [laughter]
>> Yo, if he falls on the floor, I don't
think all three of us could pick him up.
Bro,
>> you kept looking back at me. I'm like,
yeah, he's looking at me for the right
reasons. I'm going to fall down.
>> Yo, he's he's he's walking like this.
>> All I was thinking is I hope that dog
don't jump on me.
>> He's walking like this. I'm like, why is
he walking so slow, bro? Like,
>> oh man, I had a had a great time with
Ashton, huh? He did not have to eat that
hot chip. That was just total decision
up to him there at the end. And I'm glad
that he was able to at least feel better
at the end and learn something now that
he didn't know previously. And that's
the problem with trading as a whole with
when it comes to 99% of people that
don't know what trading is or don't know
about somebody that does it. They're
just scared about it and they don't
understand how simple it really is. And
it's crazy. Like I'm very in shock how
well he learned this for his first time.
Like Ashton Hall has never traded before
in his life. You guys heard it directly
from him. He's never seen a YouTube
video before. He's never traded demo.
He's never even taken a trade, right?
So, this was his literal first initial
start. And he has understood something
that took me 2 years to even comprehend.
When I was learning how to trade and
going online to figure out how to trade,
I took me so much time to learn stuff,
filter out what didn't work, learn
something again, test it, remove it,
filter out, add new things. He just got
it all on a one or two hour session on
his first time. Like that is so powerful
because you save yourself from making so
many mistakes in the markets. And that's
what I do every single week with my
students. This is my first time ever
teaching somebody live like this and
teaching somebody that knows absolutely
nothing on a one-on-one. And the fact
that he was able to learn that fast
shows how powerful my teaching is and
how powerful trading can be. Because in
my community, I literally teach this but
in a much more detailed version. This is
a very summarized way of teaching him
how to trade. We still left out
platforms. We still left out slippage
spreads, trades, pips, uh trading view,
brokers. Like there's so much we left
out. And you know, it's very long video
for me to actually teach him that. And
he didn't have to learn all that right
now to learn the direction of the
market, whether it's going to go up or
down. But I do that every single week
inside of the community with my
students. I literally teach them how to
trade. I share with them my exact
trades, why I'm interested in taking
them. They're part of a community where
they can interact with other successful
traders and ask me questions directly.
And the most valuable of all, I get to
review your trades after you take them
when you make a mistake. And I wish I
was part of a community like this when I
got started because I would literally
know from the person that I am learning
from why I made this mistake and how can
I actually learn from it. And that's
what I've been doing lately for the last
six to 12 months is really focusing more
on the traders themselves on the trades
that they're taking rather than just
teaching them what something is and
letting them to go figure it out. Like
I'm actually going hand onand with you
to do this. And sadly, my community is
not open to everybody. It really is only
on acceptance purpose. Like if you
qualify, if you're at a certain level
that makes sense for you to be part of
my community, I'll accept you. If you
have a certain drive, I'll accept you. I
just don't want it to be like I'm I'm
dragging an anchor for me to teach you
how to trade and you're basically
holding back everybody else. If you
really want to trade, my team will be
able to determine that and you can apply
down below. If you click the link down
in the description below, I will teach
you how to trade. I will get you access
to my community and I will review your
trades, but you need to apply first. Be
as truthful as possible that you can
with answering your questions because if
you're not, you simply just will get
cancelled and you won't get accepted.
There's plenty of people that want to
get in and we want to work with the
right people. But with that being said,
I hope you like and enjoyed this video,
hit that like and subscribe button. You
want to be part of my community, hit the
link in description down below. And if
you want to see other videos in my
channel, I have a 10-hour video where I
literally teach you how to trade and
give you all the other stuff that I did
not mention in this video right here.
Just hit that subscribe button, go check
out my other videos. There's so much
value just hidden inside of this channel
that it's crazy. I wish I had a channel
like this when I got started trading,
but it's here now for you guys. It is
not too late to trade. Trading will be
open forever. As long as there's
currencies in the world, there will be
markets to trade. So, don't ever think
that the markets will come to an end.
With that being said, hope you guys
enjoyed this video. Hit that like and
subscribe button and I'll see you guys
in the next